<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Youtube on David Sales</title><link>https://davidsales.pt/tags/youtube/</link><description>Recent content in Youtube on David Sales</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://davidsales.pt/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Experimenting with Youtube</title><link>https://davidsales.pt/p/experimenting-with-youtube/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://davidsales.pt/p/experimenting-with-youtube/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://davidsales.pt/p/experimenting-with-youtube/wow-very-deep.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Experimenting with Youtube" />&lt;p>&lt;strong>TL;DR&lt;/strong>: Using Youtube, and this website as well, to try and expose myself more. Will try to transition to sharing on social media, as well. So, in the end, I can try to overcome at least a little bit of this fear.
You can find a link to my channel at the end of this post.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2 id="yikes-i-have-audhd">Yikes, I have AuDHD
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Yeap, I have a mix of the two. Got a late diagnosis and I am finding things about myself everyday. I don&amp;rsquo;t want to go to such depths, I just wanted to share this with you, and to make a little more sense of the &amp;ldquo;anxiety of being perceived&amp;rdquo; part.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Here&amp;rsquo;s a fart sound to cut the seriousness&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/Q_9VMaX61nI"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="why-youtube">Why youtube
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Well, it&amp;rsquo;s the least friction path to me, or at least it feels that way. I&amp;rsquo;m going to be posting there, and only sharing it here. This way, I&amp;rsquo;m consciously exposing myself without explicitly sharing with people that know me/perceive me on a daily basis.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>That is, without sharing it on other places. When I start to feel comfortable enough, I will start being &amp;ldquo;louder&amp;rdquo; with sharing this. Perhaps posting on my other social media&amp;hellip; It might not seem like a lot, but I am already feeling a tad anxious about posting all of this (as of now I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted this website yet).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>big sidetrack&lt;/strong>: I was going to put the &amp;ldquo;it&amp;rsquo;s not much, but it&amp;rsquo;s honest work&amp;rdquo; meme, because of the reference on the last paragraph&amp;hellip; But I just found out &lt;a class="link" href="https://www.wsaz.com/2023/05/24/farmer-behind-viral-it-aint-much-its-honest-work-meme-dies-crash/?ref=okdoomer.io" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
>he died&lt;/a>, what the actual fuck, I&amp;rsquo;m shook&amp;hellip; R.I.P.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="my-first-video">My first video
&lt;/h3>&lt;p>The first full-song that I properly learned on bass. Well, proper is a stretch, it isn&amp;rsquo;t perfect, I still can&amp;rsquo;t land the last harmonic. It&amp;rsquo;s one of my favourite songs by Jaco Pastorius, I can get into that on another post. But here it is.&lt;/p>
&lt;div class="video-wrapper">
&lt;iframe loading="lazy"
src="https://www.youtube.com/embed/a40Co8DKsUI"
allowfullscreen
title="YouTube Video"
>
&lt;/iframe>
&lt;/div>
&lt;h2 id="wrapping-it-up">Wrapping it up
&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Weird sidetrack, still shook. Anyway, expect music-related stuff, because that is one of my hobbies. I play guitar and bass, and am attempting to arrange a setup to start to learn how to play drums.
This website, in a way, is also a way of exposing myself, and trying to conquer this fear. If you have anything you want so say, please let me know, I would love to read your thoughts 🙂&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>